HERE Memorabilia 6199 MB
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
HERE Memorabilia
1931-1977
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union (HERE)
6199 MB
1.5 cubic feet
1.5 linear ft.
Memorabilia.
8210311
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 19, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 22, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6199 AV: HERE Audio-Visual Materials 6199 G: HERE Graphics 6199 mf: HERE Records on Microfilm 6199 PUBS: HERE Publications 6199/001: HERE Legislative Department Files 6199/002: HERE Western Region Local Files 6199/003: HERE Organizing Department Las Vegas Strike Files 6199/003 mf: HERE Organizing Department Files on Microfilm 6199/004: HERE Locals files 6199/004 mf: HERE Locals Files on Microfilm 6199/005: HERE Communications Department Files 6199/005 P: HERE Communications Department Photographs 6199/006: HERE General Executive Board Files 6199/006 mf: HERE General Executive Board Files on Microfilm 6199/007 mf: HERE Financial Records Files on Microfilm 6199/008 mf: HERE General President's Files on Microfilm 6199/009 mf: HERE General Secretary-Treasurer's Files on Microfilm 6199/010 mf: HERE General Office Legal Files on Microfilm 6199/011 mf: HERE Official Journals on Microfilm 6199/012 mf: HERE Joint Executive Board Files on Microfilm 6199/013: HERE Historical Files 6199/013 P: HERE Historical Photographs 6199/014: HERE Conventions Files 6199/015: HERE Editor Files
Hospitality industry -- Employees -- Labor unions; Hotels -- Employees -- Labor unions; Restaurants -- Employees -- Labor unions; Hotel Employees & Restaurant Employees International Union
8210311
- HERE seal (for seal maker, broken) (Box 1, Folder 1)
- HERE sign (Box 1, Folder 2)
- HERE sign (Box 1, Folder 3)
- HERE sign (Box 1, Folder 4)
- HERE sign (Box 1, Folder 5)
- HERE sign (Box 1, Folder 6)
- HERE sign (Box 1, Folder 7)
- HERE sign (Box 1, Folder 8)
- HERE sign (Box 1, Folder 9)
- HERE sign (ripped) (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Bartenders and Beverage Dispensers Union Local 278 sign (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Wine list from Surchom's Restaurant (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Walter Conran - Membership/Constitution books (1931, 1936, 1932) (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Type "B" Agreement - The Restaurant League of NY/Chefs, Cooks, Pastry Cookies -- Agreement - Local 69, Hotel and Restaurant/United Restaurant Liquor Dealers, 1972-1977 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Scope and Contents
  2 agreement booklets
- Cafeteria Employees - By-Laws, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  6 booklets
- Constitutions for New York AFL-CIO and Hotel & Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1954- 1971 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  11 booklets
- Cafeteria Call issues, 1966-1974 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Membership Card and Monthly Stamp booklets - Hotel & Restaurant Employees and Bartenders Int'l. Union, 1931- 1948 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous booklets, 1932-1971 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Honor Roll booklets; Testimonial Dinner program, 1964-1973 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- More Cafeteria Call issues, 1970-1973 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Souvenir Journal - Cafeteria Employees Union Local 302, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Silver Anniv. Booklet - Hotel, Motel & club Voice 1963 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Constitutional Changes Proposed - booklet, 1966-1974 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Hotel & Club Employees (small pocket folder, card holder) (Box 2, Folder 14)
- HERE Medals, 1936-1951 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Labor Chief badge and a couple buttons (Box 2, Folder 16)
- HERE & AFL-CIO badges, 1947-1971 (Box 2, Folder 17)